Aviv Shapira

CUSTOMER SUCCESS MANAGER

About

A bi-lingual Customer Success Manager, Specializing in customer facing roles and customer service (3 years). My core expertise is working with people as well as my communication both in English and in Hebrew.

My two passions are gaming and photography, in which I get to express both my creative and analytical skills. Currently seeking a full time position as a B2B CSM in the tech industry.

Contact

- Israel
- avivshapira22@gmail.com
- 0546676271
- in www.linkedin.com/in/avivshapira-466561226

Skills

- Leadership
- Creative
- Adaptive
- Interpersonal skills
- Good under pressure
- Attention to detail

Languages

- Hebrew
- English

Education History

Customer Success ENTER Course, Jolt

An immersive bootcamp that provides the tools, knowledge, terminology, and methodology of a Customer Success Manager role in the High Tech industry.

High School Diploma, Israel

Work Experience

Junior Project Manager, GreenGuy Ltd.

2019-2021

- Close interactions with clients including, maintaining ongoing communication and feedback, adjusting in accordance to client needs.
- Increased work efficiency by establishing creative and efficient measurement methods.
- Improvised quick and creative solutions when wrong manufactured parts arrive at the worksite.

Line Manager, Cashier, Kibbutz Dining Room

2018-2019

- Developed relationships with external customers (non kibbutz members) to ensure "renewal" while providing excellent service.
- Memorizing kibbutz members account numbers to ensure fast and efficient service at the cash register.
- Setting up the entire dinning room every morning such as food and drinks in the "Line".
- Responsible for maintaining the "Line" while the dining room is active.

Bartender, "Black Hole" Pub

2016 - 2017

- Acquired experience with teamwork as it was essential for our success on busy nights.
- Managing high pressure situations while still understanding customer needs.
- Gained excellent "people's skill" by having clients from all over the world and engaging with them.